Pauline Frederick Papers, 1917-1990
Sophia Smith Collection, Smith College
Pauline Frederick papers
1917-1990
Frederick, Pauline
MS 183
60 boxes (33 linear ft.)
Sophia Smith Collection Smith College Northampton, MA
Journalist and war correspondent. Papers relate primarily to her professional life, including teaching and her career as journalist. Includes coverage of the Second Quebec Conference and political conventions; World War II and its aftermath; the Berlin Airlift; the Korean War; China and the UN; Dag Hammarskjold; war in the Congo; Cuban Missile Crisis; Adlai Stevenson's trip to Latin America; the Vietnam War; and the 1976 presidential debates. Material includes writings, broadcast scripts, speeches, disc recordings, films, correspondence, diaries, photographs and audio tapes.
1908 Born on 13 February in Gallitzen, Pennsylvania
1926 Graduated from Central High School, Harrisburg, Pennsylvania
1930 Graduated from American University, major in political
1931 Received M.A. in international law from American University
1931-1939 Wrote newspaper columns and reported freelance (U.S. News, North American Newspaper Alliance, Uncle Sam's Diary.
1933-1934 Taught at Fairmont Junior College, Washington, DC
1938-1944 Worked as editorial and radio assistant to H.R. Baukhage,commentator for ABC and NBC
1945 Toured China and Burma, May to August
1945-1946 Served as war correspondent for North American Newspaper Alliance, Western Newspaper Union, and H.R. Baukhage Covered Europe and the Nuremberg trials
1946 Joined ABC in June
1953 Joined NBC in June as UN correspondent
1954 Received the Alfred I. duPont Award
1955 Received the Peabody Award
1959 Elected president of the United Nations Correspondents Association
1967 Published Ten First Ladies of the World
1969 Married Charles Robbins, 31 March
1974 Retired from NBC
1975 Joined National Public Radio as foreign affairs analyst
1976 Moderated the Carter-Ford presidential debates
1980 Retired Received the Paul White Award
1990 Died 9 May, Lake Forest, Illinois
The Pauline Frederick Papers consist of 33 linear feet of correspondence, writings, printed material, broadcast scripts, broadcast and press conference transcripts, notes, writings, speeches, photographs, memorabilia, and audiovisual materials. The inclusive dates are c. 1908 to 1990, but most of the material dates from 1932 to 1980, essentially from her extremely productive professional years. The personal material consists of correspondence, diaries, scrapbooks, and early school material.
Film and audio recordings from this collection have been digitized and are available to view online (Smith campus access only).
This collection is organized into six series:
I. Professional Activities
II. Correspondence
III. Biographical Materials
IV. Photographs
V. Audiovisual Materials
VI. Oversize Materials
Appendix: Alphabetical list of Photographs of Individuals
Photographs of the following individuals are included in the Frederick Papers in Series IV. PHOTOGRAPHS under the subseries "Professional Activities," within the folders indicated here.
Abelli, Crystal (Writings)
Anderson, Hurst R. (Speeches and events, 1964-65)
Arias, Rosario de (Writings)
Arkadev, G.P. (Miscellaneous notables)
Bachke, Ragna (Writings)
Barber, General and Mrs. Edward (Speeches and events, 1960-63)
Baukhage, Hilmar Robert (NBC Radio; ABC, Interviews)
Belannde, Victor (NBC, Misc. broadcasts, Officials and colleagues)
Bernbaum, Maurice M. (NBC, Tours, A. Stevenson's trip to Latin America)
Berretta, Tomas (ABC, Tours, Uruguay)
Boehm, Charles H. (Speeches and events, 1960-63)
Born, General Charles F. (ABC, Tours, Uruguay)
Bostrom, Gertrude (Writings)
Boyd, Bertha P. (Speeches and events, 1960-63)
Brinkley, David (NBC, Programs, Convention coverage, 1956; NBC, Misc. broadcasts, Officials and colleagues)
Brooks, Ned (NBC, Programs, Convention coverage, 1956)
Bush, George (NBC, Misc. broadcasts, Officials and colleagues)
Byrnes, James F. (ABC, Interviews)
Carnes, Betty (ABC, Programs)
Castro, Fidel (Speeches and events, UNCA)
Chancellor, John (NBC, Programs, Miscellaneous; NBC, Misc. broadcasts, Officials and colleagues)
Chennault, Claire L. (War Correspondent, China)
Considine, Bob (War Correspondent, Ceylon)
Cronkite, Walter (NBC, Programs, "Meet the Press")
Crowding, Catharine (Speeches and events, 1960-63)
Crowding, Lynn (Speeches and events, 1960-63)
Debuchi, Hama (Writings)
D'Arcy, Jean (NBC, Misc. broadcasts, Officials and colleagues)
Davidson, Howard (War Correspondent, India)
Dewey, Frances E. (ABC, Programs)
Eaton, Evelyn (War Correspondent, Flying the "Hump" of the Himalayas)
Eban, Aba (NBC, Programs, "Meet the Press")
Edwards, Bob (Speeches and events, 1975-85)
Edwards, India (ABC, Programs)
El-Zayyat, Mohammed H. (NBC, Misc. broadcasts, Officials and colleagues)
Ford, Gerald (NPR, Programs, Presidential debates, 1976)
Frandsen, Tom (NBC, Misc. broadcasts, Officials and colleagues)
Franks, Oliver (ABC, Interviews)
[Frederick, Dorothy Ann?] (Speeches and events, 1966-69)
Gerity, Mr. and Mrs. James, Jr. (Speeches and events, 1960-63)
Ghorra, Eduard (Miscellaneous notables)
Goan, Walter H. (ABC, Promotion, Radio stations)
Goldberg, Arthur (NBC, Misc. broadcasts, Officials and colleagues)
Goldwater, Barry (NBC, Misc. broadcasts, Officials and colleagues)
Gould, Bruce (War Correspondent, Miscellaneous)
Grant, Taylor (ABC, Programs)
Greer, Ben (ABC, Miscellaneous)
Griffith, Les (ABC, Programs)
Gromyko, Andrei (NBC, Misc. broadcasts, Officials and colleagues; Speeches and events, 1960-63)
[Gulher?], Edmund (Speeches and events, 1970-73)
Hammarskjold, Dag (NBC, Misc. broadcasts, Officials and colleagues)
Henry, Bill (NBC, Programs, Convention coverage, 1956
Hunt, Senator [Lester Callaway?] (ABC, Programs)
Ibarra, Jose Maria Velasco (NBC, Tours, A. Stevenson's trip to Latin America)
Irene of Greece, Princess (ABC, Programs)
Jernigan, C.C. (ABC, Promotion, Radio stations)
Jhabvala, Darius [?] (Speeches and events, undated)
Kelly, Grace (Awards, 1968-81, n.d.)
Kennedy, Edward (NBC, Misc. broadcasts, Officials and colleagues)
King, Coretta (Awards, 1968-81, n.d.)
Langston, Audrey (NBC, Misc. broadcasts, Officials and colleagues)
Lelaulu, Lelei (NPR, Programs "World Chronicle")
Lindsay, Lady (Writings)
Lord, Bishop John Wesley (Speeches and events, 1964-65)
Lowe, Eric H. (NBC, Programs, Miscellaneous)
Madariaga, Constance de (Writings)
Mahoney, Claude (NBC, Misc. broadcasts, Officials and colleagues)
Mahoney, Senator [?] (ABC, Programs)
Malone, Ted (ABC, Programs; ABC, Interviews)
Marcos, Imelda (NBC, Programs, "Meet the Press")
Martenson, Jan (NPR, Programs, "World Chronicle")
Maxwell, Alex (ABC, Interviews)
May, Madelaine (Writings)
Mbamba, Abdullah (NPR, Programs, "World Chronicle")
McCormick, John (NBC, Misc. broadcasts, Officials and colleagues)
Mead, Margaret (Awards, 1968-81, n.d.)
Molotov, Vyachaslev M. (NBC, Misc. broadcasts, Officials and colleagues)
Morgan, Edward (Speeches and events, 1975-85)
Mountbatten, Louis (War Correspondent, Ceylon)
Naval, Rey (NPR, Programs, "World Chronicle")
Pahlavi, Mohammed Reza Shah (Speeches and events, 1964-65)
Pao, General (War Correspondent, China)
Pendleton, Barbara (Speeches and events, 1960-63)
Peter, Jeanne (Writings)
Pius, Pope (War Correspondent, Italy)
Prochnik, Gretchen (Writings)
Rash, Bryson (ABC, Programs)
Recinos, Maria de (Writings)
Reece, Carroll (ABC, Programs)
Reeves, John M. (Speeches and events, 1964-65)
Rikhye, Indar Jit (Speeches and events, 1970-73)
Ritchie, David (NBC, Misc. broadcasts, Officials and colleagues)
Robbins, Charles (NBC, Misc. broadcasts, Officials and colleagues)
Romani, [ ? ] (of Malaysia) (NBC, Misc. broadcasts, Officials and colleagues)
Romulo, Carlos P. (NPR, Programs, "World Chronicle")
Roosevelt, Franklin D. (Miscellaneous notables)
Rosenthal, Abe (NBC, Misc. broadcasts, Officials and colleagues)
Sacasa, Maria de (Writings)
Sarnoff, David (NBC, Misc. broadcasts, Officials and colleagues)
Saxton, Brian E. (NPR, Programs, "World Chronicle")
Scali, John (NBC, Misc. broadcasts, Officials and colleagues)
Schick, Jules (ABC, Miscellaneous)
Selassie, Haile (NBC, Tours, Ethiopia)
Sobolev, Arkady Aleksandrovich (NBC, Misc. broadcasts, Officials and colleagues; Miscellaneous notables)
Stevenson, Adlai (NBC, Programs, "Meet the Press"; NBC, Tours, A. Stevenson's trip to Latin America; NBC, Misc. broadcasts, Officials and colleagues)
Stoker, Carroll (ABC, Miscellaneous)
Swanson, Claude (Freelance)
Thant, U (NBC, Misc. broadcasts, Officials and colleagues; Miscellaneous notables)
Tsarapkin, Semyon (Miscellaneous notables)
Van de Veu, Madame (Europe, 1945-46, Belgium)
Vasilits, Valentin (NPR, Programs, "World Chronicle")
von Prittwitz, Marieluise (Writings)
Vredenburgh, Dorothy (ABC, Programs)
Wald, Dick (NBC, Misc. broadcasts, Officials and colleagues)
[Warren, Earl?] (Speeches and events, n.d.)
Wedemeyer, General (War Correspondent, China)
Wu, Pao-Fang (Writings)
Young, Andrew (NBC, Misc. broadcasts, Officials and colleagues)
Information on Use
Terms of Access and Use
The papers are open to research according to the regulations of the Sophia Smith Collection without any additional restrictions.
Additional Formats
Film and audio recordings from this collection have been digitized and are available to view online (Smith campus access only).
History of the Collection
Pauline Frederick Robbins donated her papers in four installments between 1985 and 1987.
Search Terms
Baukhage, Hilmar R. (Hilmar Robert), b. 1889; Frederick, Pauline; Stevenson, Adlai E. (Adlai Ewing), 1900-1965; Thant, U, 1909-1974; Hammarskjold, Dag, 1905-1961; Meir, Golda, 1898-1978; ABC News--History--Sources; American University (Washington, D.C.)--Students--History--Sources; Broadcast journalism--United States--History--Sources; Korean War, 1950-53--Journalists; Political conventions--United States--History--20th century--Sources; Radio journalism--United States--History--Sources; Vietnamese Conflict, 1961-1975--Journalists--Sources; War correspondents--United States--History--Sources; World War, 1939-1945--Journalists--Sources; National Public Radio (U.S.)--History--Sources; NBC News--History--Sources; Nuremberg Trial of Major German War Criminals, Nuremberg, Germany, 1945-1946--Sources; United Nations. Correspondents Association--History--Sources; Women journalists--United States--History--20th century--Sources; China--Foreign relations--20th century--Sources; Congo (Democratic Republic)--History--Civil War, 1960-1965--Journalists; Berlin (Germany)--History--Blockade, 1948-1949--Sources; Cuban Missile Crisis, Oct. 1962--Journalists
- Series I. PROFESSIONAL ACTIVITIES 1931-85, undated
  The first six subseries, from Fairmont Junior College through National Public Radio, follow Frederick's career from 1931 to 1980. There are some examinations and printed material from her year teaching at Fairmont Junior College in 1933-34. Her work as assistant to H.R. Baukhage is represented by notes from her coverage of the second Quebec Conference in 1944; programs, notes, and memorabilia from the national political conventions in 1944; one script from 1941; and miscellaneous correspondence, 1938-40. The War Correspondent subseries dates from 1945 to 1946, when she was working free-lance for the North American Newspaper Alliance, the Western Newspaper Union, and H.R. Baukhage. It contains correspondence, articles, reports, memorabilia, and clippings from Frederick's China/Burma trip, her work in Europe, and the Nuremberg trials. The ABC, NBC, and National Public Radio subseries contain correspondence, broadcast scripts and transcripts, interviews, notes, UN documents, and memorabilia related to her work for these networks between 1946 and 1980. These subseries concern programs and special events, press conferences, official tours, contract and inter-office business, publicity, and specific subjects. Among the many events covered during these years were the Berlin Airlift, the Korean War, China and the UN, Dag Hammarskjold, the Congo war, the Cuban missile crisis, Adlai Stevenson's trip to Latin America, and the Vietnam War. Of special interest in these sections, are Frederick's original broadcasts and interviews, the subject sections, and NBC correspondence and reports to William McAndrew (her boss.)
  The Other Activities subseries consists of correspondence, scripts, printed material, publicity, meeting agendas, and notes related to various organizations in which Frederick was involved from 1942 to 1984. There is substantial material from her term as president of the United Nations Correspondents Association in 1959.
  The Speeches and Events subseries contains the texts, related correspondence, publicity, and itineraries for her busy lecture schedule, 1931-85.
  The Writings subseries reflects Frederick's career as a writer and columnist. It contains typescripts, clippings, printed articles, notes, and correspondence. These materials relate to her newspaper columns "Women in Official Life" (1932) and "Women of Diplomacy" (1932), various articles she wrote from the 1930s to the 1980s (particularly for the North American Newspaper Alliance and U.S. News in the 1930s), portions of a book to which she contributed (published in 1941 as America Prepares for Tomorrow), and Ten First Ladies of the World, which she wrote and published in 1967. The texts of reports Frederick wrote as a war correspondent are located in this subseries.
- Series II. CORRESPONDENCE 1936-86, undated
  Frederick's professional correspondence consists of letters from fans and listeners, invitations, correspondence with notable persons, and letters related to specific subjects. Those from fans and listeners are of particular interest because they contain comments (both of praise and criticism) on specific interviews and programs as well as general letters from her wide and appreciative audience. The personal correspondence is with friends and family. Of particular interest are the letters from Frederick to her long-time friend Ann Cordell (1950-1963) and the early letters to her sister, Catharine Crowding (1941-1946), which contain detailed descriptions of her experience overseas. The business correspondence contains her sister's letters concerning Frederick's business affairs during the period 1945 to 1946 and a group of miscellaneous business-related papers.
- Series III. BIOGRAPHICAL MATERIAL 1917-90, undated
  The Articles and Clippings date from 1948 to 1984 and are a miscellaneous group of materials about Frederick. The early diaries (1940s, 1950s) are incomplete, but are detailed for the short time spans that they cover. The diaries dating from 1968 to 1984 are appointment calendars used as diaries. The School and College material dates from 1917 and consists of school compositions, clippings, memorabilia, grade reports, and writings from grammar school, junior high school, high school, and college. Her master's thesis from American University is included in this subseries. The Awards and Honorary Degrees subseries consists of correspondence, publicity, and printed material related to the many awards Frederick received between 1950 and 1985.
- Series IV. PHOTOGRAPHS circa 1908-1985, undated
  This series contains approximately 4200 photographs, the majority of which relate to Pauline Frederick's professional activities, and include many of her colleagues, and the officials and celebrities with whom she came into contact during her long career. The bulk of these are from World War II on--there are few from her earliest professional years. There is also a smaller number of photographs of her personal activities, including childhood, school, family, and vacation pictures.
- Series V. AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS 1945-80, undated
  There are approximately 90 sound recordings (divided into three subseries, Phonograph Records, Cassette Tapes, and Reel-to-reel Tapes) which for the most part selectively document Frederick's radio and television broadcasting career, primarily during the ABC through NPR years. Others are of speeches, award programs, and other professional events. There are also tapes of interviews of Frederick by others and of her 1969 wedding. Most of the cassettes are duplicates of the reel-to-reel tapes, copied for research use but there are a few unique tapes in both categories. The Films subseries contains 8 reels of film (16, 8, and 35 mm.) of miscellaneous broadcasts, interviews, and events.
- Series VI. OVERSIZE MATERIALS 1945-77, undated
  This series consists of a small number of posters, awards, honorary degrees, and photographs that have been separated from like materials because of their size.
- Series I. PROFESSIONAL ACTIVITIES
  - Fairmont Junior College (Washington DC): journalism exams, clippings, and "Fairmont Follies," 1933-34 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Editorial Assistant to H.R. Baukhage, Commentator for ABC and NBC Radio
    - Second Quebec Conference: notes, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - National convention coverage (Chicago): notes, programs, and memoranda, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Program: "Let's Talk It Over," 1939-40, undated
      - Scripts and transcripts (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Broadcast: script, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1938-40 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - War Correspondent (North American Newspaper Alliance, Western Newspaper Union, ABC), 1945-46
    - United Nations Charter Commission: notes, Apr-May 1945 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - China/Burma trip, May-Aug 1945
      - Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 9)
      - Typescripts of articles (Box 1, Folder 10)
      - Memorabilia, itineraries, and interview (Box 1, Folder 11)
      - Clippings (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Europe/Nuremberg, Sep 1945-Jun 1946
      - Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 13)
      - Articles, wireless reports, and notes
        - Poland (Box 1, Folder 14)
        - Nuremberg (Box 1, Folder 15)
        - France (Box 1, Folder 16)
        - Germany (Box 1, Folder 17)
        - Copenhagen and Brussels (Box 1, Folder 18)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 1, Folder 19)
      - Memorabilia (Box 1, Folder 20)
      - Clippings (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Queen Mary troopship coverage: wire copies, and memorabilia, 1946, [see also BIOGRAPHICAL MATERIAL, diary, 1946] (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Queen Elizabeth maiden voyage: correspondence, clippings, and memorabilia, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Return of the Viet Stoss Altar, Cracow, Poland: correspondence and memorabilia, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1944, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - ABC
    - News broadcasts: scripts, [see also AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS]
      - 1946-Nov 1952 (Box 2, Folder 1-7)
      - Dec 1952-1953, undated (Box 3, Folder 1-2)
    - Programs
      - "Consent of the Governed": script, 4 Jul 1949, [see also AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS] (Box 3, Folder 3)
      - Philadelphia presidential convention and election: publicity, wire copies, and memorabilia, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      - Chicago presidential convention and election: publicity and memoranda, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 5)
      - "If You Were President": program proposal, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 6)
      - "Pauline Frederick's Feature Story": script, 9 Feb 1949 (Box 3, Folder 7)
      - "Pauline Frederick's Guest Book": scripts, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 8)
      - "Pauline Frederick Reports": publicity, formats, 1949-52 (Box 3, Folder 9)
      - "Pick a Date With Buddy Rogers": script, 17 Jan 1950 (Box 3, Folder 10)
      - "Town Meeting of the Air": script, notes, 1951-52 (Box 3, Folder 11)
      - Truman Inauguration: press releases, schedule, and memorabilia, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 12)
      - "Vacation Time": publicity and scripts, 1950, [see also AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS] (Box 3, Folder 13)
      - "World Security Workshop": script and clippings, 2 Nov 1947 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Memorabilia, 1946-53, undated (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Press conferences and interviews, 1950, [see also AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS] (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Tours (official)
      - Uruguay (inauguration of President Beretta): correspondence and memorabilia, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 17)
      - Europe: correspondence, scripts, and memorabilia, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 18)
      - Radio stations KELD, Arkansas; WARM, Scranton, PA; and WNAT, MS, 1951-52, [see PHOTOGRAPHS] (Box 3)
      - U.S. Navy tour to Hawaii: publicity and memorabilia, Feb 1953 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence
      - Contract and employment, 1948-53 (Box 3, Folder 20)
      - Interoffice, 1946-53 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Publicity, 1949-53 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Subjects
      - Berlin Blockade: notes, passes, and wire copies, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 23)
      - China: memoranda and notes, 1950-53 (Box 3, Folder 24)
      - Korea: notes, UN documents, and wire copies, 1950-52 (Box 3, Folder 25)
      - Malaya: notes, undated (Box 3, Folder 26)
      - Big Four Peace Treaty, Trieste: notes, 1947? (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - NBC
    - News broadcasts: scripts (includes "Pauline Frederick Reporting," "Emphasis," "Monitor," and "Nightly News"), [see also AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS]
      - 1953-Sep 1954 (Box 4, Folder 1-6)
      - Oct 1954-May 1955 (Box 5, Folder 1-8)
      - Jun 1955-1956 (Box 6, Folder 1-9)
      - 1957-59 (Box 7, Folder 1-8)
      - 1960-Jun 1961 (Box 8, Folder 1-7)
      - Jul 1961-Sep 1962 (Box 9, Folder 1-8)
      - Oct 1962-1967 (Box 10, Folder 1-11)
      - 1968-[1974?], undated (Box 11, Folder 1-11)
    - Programs
      - "Africa: 5 Minutes to 12: Special Report": scripts, Feb 1961 (Box 11, Folder 12)
      - "Comment": script, 3 Aug 1958 (Box 11, Folder 13)
      - U.S. presidential convention coverage: articles, memorabilia, script, and wire copies, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 14)
      - "Death of a Statesman" (Dag Hammarskjold), 1961
        - Script (Box 11, Folder 15)
        - Articles and clippings (Box 11, Folder 16)
        - Correspondence (including condolence letters and cards to Pauline Frederick), 1961-62 (Box 11, Folder 17)
      - "Discussion": script, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 18)
      - "Emphasis": publicity and memoranda, 1960, undated, [see also AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS] (Box 11, Folder 19)
      - "Eternal Light": correspondence, publicity, and scripts, 1964-66 (Box 11, Folder 20)
      - "Frontiers of Faith": script and publicity, Sep 1954 (Box 12, Folder 1)
      - "Have You a Question?": scripts, Jun-Jul 1960 (Box 12, Folder 2)
      - "Image Russia": scripts, 1953-59 (Box 12, Folder 3)
      - "Jack Paar Show" (Pauline Frederick as guest): script, 1960 (Box 12, Folder 4)
      - "Listen to the Witness," 1954, [see also AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS]
        - Publicity, correspondence, and miscellaneous (Box 12, Folder 5)
        - Scripts and related material (Box 12, Folder 6)
      - "Meet the Press"
        - Transcripts
          - 1955-67 (Box 12, Folder 7-10)
          - 1968-71 (Box 13, Folder 1)
        - Correspondence, 1967, 1969, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 2)
      - "Monitor": publicity, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 3)
      - "Open Mind": transcripts, 1963, 1965, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 4)
      - "Pauline Frederick Reporting": publicity, 1953-55, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 5)
      - Pope Paul VI visit to the UN, 1965
        - Press releases (Box 13, Folder 6)
        - Correspondence from viewers (Box 13, Folder 7)
        - Technical directions and transcripts (Box 13, Folder 8)
      - "Projection 59": transcript, 1959? (Box 13, Folder 9)
      - "Purex Special for Women"
        - Promotion and publicity, 1960-61 (Box 13, Folder 10)
        - "The Problem Child": transcript, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 11)
      - "So You Want to Go to Europe": script, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 12)
      - "Today Show", [see also AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS] (Box 13)
        - Transcripts
          - 1958-69 (Box 13, Folder 13-14)
          - 1970-73 (Box 14, Folder 1)
        - Golda Meir interview: correspondence, Oct 1969, [see also transcript for 30 Sep 1969] (Box 14, Folder 2)